export const questionNoIdea = () => {
    return [
        {
            question: "What is Takaful?",
            wrong: "A policy that shifts the risk to the insurance company.",
            correct: "Mutual cooperation",
        },
        {
            question: "Is Takaful comply with Shariah law?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Low rate and financial risk management is why you should take takaful at young age.",
            wrong: "False",
            correct: "True",
        },
        {
            question: "How many should I contribute to takaful?",
            wrong: "All of my money!!!.",
            correct: "Advisable 5-7% from income",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful can provide the coverage and benefits similar to conventional insurance?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful is free from interest (Riba)? ",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful is free from uncertainty (Gharar)?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },

    ]
}

export const questionBasic = () => {
    return [
        {
            question: "One of the difference between takaful and conventional insurance is mutual risk is shared amongst the participants?",
            wrong: "False",
            correct: "True",
        },
        {
            question: "All takaful plan provide full life protection?",
            wrong: "Absolutely",
            correct: "No, every plan is difference",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the waiting period for the coverage to go into full effect?",
            wrong: "7 days",
            correct: "30 days",
        },
        {
            question: "What factor should I NOT include in considering for a takaful?",
            wrong: "Financial commitments",
            correct: "Higher profit",
        },
        {
            question: "Is takaful also financial management for future risk?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Panel hospitals are recommended for easier claiming process?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful only cover cost from selected panel hospitals?",
            wrong: "True",
            correct: "False",
        },
    ]
}

export const questionAverage = () => {
    return [
        {
            question: "Takaful is suitable for anyone regardless of religion?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "All takaful plan provide full protection?",
            wrong: "Absolutely",
            correct: "No, every plan is difference",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the waiting period for the coverage to go into full effect?",
            wrong: "7 days",
            correct: "30 days",
        },
        {
            question: "To get better deal, I should lie my current health condition. They will not find out?",
            wrong: "For sure!",
            correct: "No. There is waiting period. On top of that they will start investigation.",
        },
        {
            question: "Is takaful cover existing condition?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Mutual assistance is important aspect in takafull?",
            wrong: "No",
            correct: "Yes",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful only cover cost from selected panel hospitals?",
            wrong: "False",
            correct: "True",
        },
        {
            question: "Takaful consider as luxury?",
            wrong: "Yes",
            correct: "No",
        },
    ]
}